Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 1
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 1
- Box: 19, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: The Government, Industrial Relations and Economic Development in Japan, 1964; Publication (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Wage Problems in Japan, 1962; Publication (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Characteristics of the Japanese Teachers Union, 1965; Publication (Box 19, Folder 6)
    Author: Taishiro Shirai
- Box: 19, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: correspondence (Sophia Socio-Econ.Institute, Ballon/Sakurabayashi), 1964; Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
    Notes: letter
  - Item 2: Personnel Administration in Modern Japan - Historical Development, 1962; Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Some Data on Industrial Relations in Japan, 1964; Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: The Labor Movement in 1961, 1962; Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: The New Japan: A Rising Class Asks 'Where is Our Dream?', Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
    Notes: news paper article
  - Item 6: The New Japan: Ex-Enemy is Now Major U.S. Ally in East, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: The New Japan: Nation Emerges From War Sharply Divided, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Box: 19, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: African-American Labor Center, Institute of Tailoring and Cutting, Kenya, Publication (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Collective Bargaining Agreement between Caltex (Africa) Limited and the Kenya Petroleum Oil Workers Union covering terms and conditions of service for the labour employees of Caltex (Africa) Ltd. In Kenya, 1961; Publication (Box 19, Folder 8)
    Author: Caltex (Africa) Ltd.
  - Item 3: Collective Bargaining Agreement Between East African Road Services Limited and Transport and Allied Workers Union (Kenya): Setting out terms and conditions of Service for Employees, 1961; Publication (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Collective Bargaining Agreement Between East African Road Services Limited and Trasport and Allied Workers Union (Kenya): Setting out terms and conditions of Service for Employees, 1961; Publication (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Learning Skills in Kenya, 1963; Publication (Box 19, Folder 8)
    Author: Maida Springer
  - Item 6: Memorandum of an Agreement of Terms and conditions of employment negotiated between employees and management of the East African Breweries, Limited Kenya, 1961; Publication (Box 19, Folder 8)
    Author: East African Breweries Limited
  - Item 7: Kenya: An Economic Survey, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 8)
    Author: Barclays Bank (Dominion, Colonial, and Overseas)
  - Item 8: The Kenya Institute of Administration, Publication (Box 19, Folder 8)
    Author: Kenya Institute of Administration
- Box: 19, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1961; Publication (Box 19, Folder 9)
    Author: Federation of Korean Trade Unions
  - Item 2: Korean Journal of Public Administration, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 9)
    Author: Soul Taehakkyo. Haengjong Taehagwon
    Notes: v.4:no.1
  - Item 3: Korean Journal of Public Administration, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.4:no.2
  - Item 4: Collective Agreement between Korean National Railway and Korean Railway Workers' Union, 1963; Publication (Box 19, Folder 9)
    Author: Korean Railway Workers' Union; Korean National Railway
  - Item 5: Constitution and Collective Agreement, 1963; Publication (Box 19, Folder 9)
    Notes: Amended at the 1963 Congress, September 30, 1963.
- Box: 19, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Spanish-Language Labor Books Stocked by RTAC, 1959; Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Spanish-Language Publications on Labor Matters, Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Trade Unionism in the Free World: Table of Contents, Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Usis Labor Bibliography: Publications and Films.Industrial Relations, 1962; Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
    Notes: list/bibl.
- Box: 19, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Unemployment in Antigua: A ReportAntigua in the British Leeward Islands, 1952; Publication (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: The Leeward Islands: An Economic Survey, 1964; Publication (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Box: 19, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Constitution and Bye-Laws of the.General Workers Union of Liberia, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
    Author: National Maritime, Seamen and General Workers Union of Liberia
  - Item 2: National Maritime and Dock-Workers C.I.O. of Liberia: Nat'l Membership Card, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
    Notes: membership card
- Box: 19, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Libya: An Economic Survey, 1965; Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Box: 19, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Budget de la Communaute pour le deuxieme excercice, 1963; Publication (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Die Neue Sozialversicherungs-Ordung, 1947; Publication (Box 19, Folder 14)
    Author: Luxembourg (Grand Duchy)
  - Item 3: Die Sozialversicherung in Luxemburg, 1946; Publication (Box 19, Folder 14)
    Author: Freie Letzeburger Arbechterverband
  - Item 4: L'Organisation et le Fonctionnementen France et au Luxembourg, 1951; Publication (Box 19, Folder 14)
    Author: Pierre Camy
  - Item 5: Miners' & Steelworkers' Unions in the European Coal & Steel Community, 1956; Publication (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: Rapport Politique, 1965; Publication (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Dix Annees de Marche Commun Charbon-Acier: 1953-1963, Publication (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Box: 19, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Malawi: An Economic Survey, 1965; Publication (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Box: 19, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Annual Report and Statement of Accounts, 1965; Publication (Box 19, Folder 16)
    Author: Bank Negara Malaysia
  - Item 2: General Council's Report 1963-1964, Publication (Box 19, Folder 16)
    Author: Malaysian Trades Union Congress
- Box: 19, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Role of Labour in Developing and UtilisingEconomic Growth in Asia, 1962; Publication (Box 19, Folder 17)
    Author: P. P. Narayanan
  - Item 2: National Union of Plantation Workers: A Talk by P.P. Narayanan to the Economics Students of the U. of Malaya, 1957; Publication (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Malaya's Biggest Union, 1957; Publication (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Annual Report and Statement of Accounts, 1961; Publication (Box 19, Folder 17)
    Author: Bank of Negara Malaysia
  - Item 5: Annual Report and Statement of Accounts, 1962; Publication (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Box: 19, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Rules and Constitution: All malayan Estates Staff Union, Publication (Box 19, Folder 18)
    Author: Malayan Estates Staff Union
  - Item 2: Constitution of the National Union of Plantation Workers, Malaya, Publication (Box 19, Folder 18)
    Author: National Union of Plantation Workers
  - Item 3: Constitution of the National Union of Plantation Workers, Malaya, Publication (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Trade Unions in Malaya, 1957; Publication (Box 19, Folder 18)
    Author: Parmer J. Norman
  - Item 5: Malayan Trades Union Congress, 1962; Publication (Box 19, Folder 18)
    Author: Malayan Trades Union Congress
    Notes: souvenir issue
  - Item 6: Report on MTUC Education Work 1961-1962, Publication (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Plantation House: Headquarters of the National UnionOfficial Opening, 1957; Publication (Box 19, Folder 18)
    Notes: conference programme
  - Item 8: Annual Report and Statement of Accounts/Laporan Tahunan dan Penyata Kira2, 1960; Publication (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Item 9: Annual Report and Statement of Accounts, 1961; Publication (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Box: 20, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Press Release No. 9: U.S. SectionRights Under Contract Labor Program, 1956; Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Author: Joint United States-Mexico Trade Union Committee
    Notes: press release
  - Item 2: Machismo, 1962; Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Author: Armando Ayala Anguiano
  - Item 3: Foreign Labor Information: Labor in Mexico, 1958; Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Party, Government and the Labor Movement in Mexico: Two Case Studies, 1964; Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Box: 20, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Ras Tafari Movement in Kingston, Jamaica, 1960; Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Mexican Labor News, 1940-1941 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Author: Universidad Obrera de Mexico
  - Item 3: Mexican Labor News, 1942; Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Notes: August 11, 1942.
  - Item 4: Mexican Labor News, 1942; Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Notes: December 15, 1942.
  - Item 5: Mexican Labor News, 1942; Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Notes: February 17, 1942.
  - Item 6: Mexican Labor News, 1943; Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Notes: March 2, 1943.
  - Item 7: Mexican Labor News, 1942; Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Notes: May 12, 1942.
  - Item 8: Mexican Labor News, 1945; Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Notes: May 17, 1945.
  - Item 9: Mexican Labor News, 1942; Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Notes: May 6, 1942.
- Box: 20, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Boletin de la Asociacion Iberoamericana'Manualesdel Personal', 1954; Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Boletin Tecnico Diciembre 1959: 'La Ley Federal del Trabajo', Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Caminos de la Unidad: IntervencionIndustrias Metalurgicas y Mecanicas, 1958; Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Contrato Colectivo de Trabajo celebrado entrela Republica Mexicana, 1957; Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Contrato Colectivo de Trabajo ObligatarioAlgodon y sus Mixturas, 1950; Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Diez Anos de Relaciones Industriales, 1958; Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Author: Instituto Tecnologico y de Estudios Superiores de Monterrey. Departamento de Relaciones Industriales
  - Item 7: El Escalafon y sus Efectos, 1949; Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Author: Instituto Tecnologico y de Estudios Superiores de Monterrey
  - Item 8: El Trabajo a Domicilio en Mexico, 1949; Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: La C.T.M. y la Carestia de la Vida, 1937; Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Author: Confederacion de Trabajadores de Mexico
  - Item 10: La Iniciativa Privada y el Desarrolla Economico del Pais, Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Author: COPARMEX (Organization: Mexico)
  - Item 11: La Organizacion Patronal en Mexico, 1947; Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: La Productividad y las Relaciones Humanas, Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Las Empresas de Servicios Publicos y la Ley Federal del Trabajo, 1950; Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Author: Euquerio Guerrero
  - Item 14: No Hay Revolucion sin Libertad, Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Author: Luis Alberto Monge
  - Item 15: Que es la Federacion de SindicatosMetas immediatas y mediatas, 1960; Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: Inter-American Management Conference, 1961; Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Box: 20, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Boletin de la Asociacion Iberoamericana'ElDirigentes Industriales', 1954; Publication (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Codigo de Seguridad Social, 1947; Publication (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Author: Mexico
  - Item 3: Conferencia Regional LatinoamericanaAmerica Latina en 1970, Publication (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Conferencia Regional LatinoamericanaAmerica Latina en 1970, Publication (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Facts and Figures: Mexico and its Labor Movement, 1958; Publication (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Facts and Figures: Some Economic DiscontentsLimited Survey, 1958; Publication (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: IV Congreso Internacional de Estudiantes, 1956; Publication (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: La Doctrina Obrera del Regimen, 1959; Publication (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Party, Government and the Labor Movement in Mexico: Two Case Studies, 1964; Publication (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Paz en la Tierra con agrado del Pueblo, 1949; Publication (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Centro Interamericano de Estudios de Seguridad Social, 1963; Publication (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Author: Instituto Mexicano del Seguro Social
  - Item 12: Funciones del Departamento de Personal, 1950; Publication (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Author: Rafael Paez
  - Item 13: Reality of an ORIT Dream - the Inter-American Labor College, Publication (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Author: Arturo jauregui hurtado
- Box: 20, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Canasta de Precios al MenudeoTlaxcala y sus Indices Respectivos, 1967; Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Author: Mexico. Secretaria de Industria y Comercio. Direccion General de Muestreo
  - Item 2: The Labor Movement in Mexico (From the RevolutionLazaro Gardenas), 1970; Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Author: Carlos Planck
  - Item 3: Publicacoines de la Division de Recursos Humanos, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Notes: list/bibliography
  - Item 4: Combate: Homenaje a la Revolucion Mexicana, 1960; Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Contrato Colectivo de TrabajoSimilares de la Republica Mexicana, 1951; Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Labor Legislation and Mexican Industrial Relations, 1968; Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Author: Richard U. Miller
  - Item 7: Intercambios, Bulletin #4, July 1967, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Author: Education and World Affairs. Study Project on U.S. -Mexican Educational Relations
  - Item 8: Labor and the Alliance, 1963; Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Important Labor Move, 1963; Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Author: John Herling
  - Item 10: Speech Delivered on Behalf of the OASMexico City, January 8, 1963, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Notes: speech
- Box: 20, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Change in Latin America: The Mexican and Cuban Revolutions, 1960; Publication (Box 20, Folder 6)
    Author: Daniel Cosio Villegas
  - Item 2: Contrato Colectivo de Trabajo, 1965; Publication (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Contrato Colectivo de Trabajo celebrado entre PetroleosMexicana, 1967; Publication (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Informacion Laborista Extranjera: LegislacionProvisiones Seleccionadas, 1958; Publication (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: La IV Reunion de la Comision ConsultivaTrabajadores Intelectuales, 1957; Publication (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Mexico: Trabajo y Desarrolla Economico, 1961; Publication (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Scientific, Engineering and Technical Education in Mexico, 1967; Publication (Box 20, Folder 6)
    Author: Russell G. Davis
  - Item 8: The Teaching of Economics in Mexico, 1967; Publication (Box 20, Folder 6)
    Author: Blanca M. de Petricioli
- Box: 20, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Contrato Colectivo de Trabajo celebrado entre PetroleosMexicana, 1963; Publication (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Contrato Colectivo de Trabajo y Reglamento Interior 1963-1965, Publication (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Contrato Colectivo de Trabajo: Obligatario parala Republica Mexicana, 1964; Publication (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Estatutos de la Federacion de Trabajadores: Principios, Programa, 1962; Publication (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Los Partidos Politicos en Mexico, 1961; Publication (Box 20, Folder 7)
    Author: Hector Solis Quiroga
  - Item 6: The Mexican Oil Strike of 1937, Publication (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Box: 20, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: La Legislation du Travail au Moyen-Orient, Publication (Box 20, Folder 8)
    Author: Zaki Badaoui
  - Item 2: Position de la CGTL face a la Situation Actuelle, 1983; Publication (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Trade Union Problems: The Middle East, 1962; Publication (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Trade Union Problems: The Middle East, 1962; Publication (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Two Centers of Arab Power, 1959; Publication (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Box: 20, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Naissance du Syndicalisme Marocain 20 Mars 1955, Publication (Box 20, Folder 9)
    Author: Union marocaine du travail
- Box: 20, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Richtlijnen betreffende lessen, welke in en buitenworden gegeven, 1952; Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
    Language: Dutch.
  - Item 2: Richtlynenmap, Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: De jonge Arbeiders en de Arbeidersbeweging van dee tijd, Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Declaration of Principles adopted by the XVIth Congressat Luxembourg, 1968; Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: European Regional Organisation of the I.C.F.T.U., Euro. Regional Conf., 1961; Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Federatie Nederlandse Vakbeweging (Confed. Nth. Trade Union Movement), 1976; Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Foundation of Labour: The Netherlands buildsvoluntary cooperation, Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Information Bulletin of the Netherlands Federation of Trade Unions No. 107, 1975; Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Information Bulletin of the Netherlands Federation of Trade Unions No. 108, 1975; Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Survey of the Earlier CongressesChristian Trade Union Movement, 1952; Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
    Author: International Federation of Christian Trade Unions
  - Item 11: Toespraak van W. Kok, vorrzitter vanMadrid, 19-23 November 1979, Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Box: 20, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: 10 jaar, Stichting van den Arbeid, Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Contact, 1954; Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: De Kleine Gids, 1949; Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Employers and Employers AssociationsIndustrial Relations System, 1967; Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Foundatin of Labour in the Netherlands, Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
    Author: Foundation of Labour
  - Item 6: Foundation of Labour in the Netherlands, Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Het Moderne Arbeidsrecht: Rede Uitgesproken(28 Mei 1935), Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Legal Restriction on Employment Termination in the Netherlands, 1967; Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Life isn't all beer and skittles, 1976; Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
    Author: Industriebond NVV
  - Item 10: Postwar Wage Determination in the Netherlands, 1957; Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Item 11: Statuten: Van Het Christelijk Nationaal Vakverbond in Nederland, 1957; Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Box: 20, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: correspondence (Bateman, N.V. Magazijn), 1951; Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Inleiding voor Mentorengids II., Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: IOJ: A Professional Organization or a Communist Propaganda Instrument?, 1963; Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: L'industrie de tabac et cigares dans les Pays-Basappreteurs de tabac, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Outlines van de Lessen Verkoopkunde, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Overzicht van de programma's van de cursussenpaktafel worden gegeven, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: Taak van de Verkoopchef, 1952; Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: Wat zij is en wat zij doet, 1967; Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Box: 20, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: De Kunst van het Geven en wat u daarvan moet weten, Publication (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Collectieve Arbeidsovereenkomst, 1951; Publication (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Collectieve Arbeidsovereenkomst, 1963; Publication (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Collectieve Arbeidsovereenkomst voor de Tuinbouwhet contractjaar, 1951; Publication (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Contract for staff and regular employees betweenLago Employee Council, 1958; Publication (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: International University Contact for Management Education, Publication (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Internationale Federatie van ChristelijkeTransport-arbeidersbonden, 1946; Publication (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Landelijke Collectieve Arbeidsovereenkomst voor het Stukadoorsbedrijf, 1939; Publication (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: Wenken voor chauffers en emballeurs, Publication (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: Report of the activities of the Contactgroep Opvoering Productiviteit (Netherlands Productivity Center) // Two Years of COP, 1954; Publication (Box 20, Folder 13)
    Author: Contactgroep Opvoering Productiviteit
- Box: 20, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Problems in Industrial Relations in Underdeveloped Territories, 1952; Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: The Ibos go it alone, 1967; Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Behind Nigeria's Revolt, 1966; Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
    Author: Martin Kilson
  - Item 4: Colonialism and Trade UnionismNigeria: A Comparative Study, 1966; Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
    Author: Joel Kaplan
  - Item 5: A System Analysis ApproachResource Development Planning: Nigeria, 1967; Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: Facts about Nigeria, 10. Labour, 1963; Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
    Author: Nigeria. Federal Ministry of Information
  - Item 7: From Ashby to Reconstruction: Manpower and Education in Nigeria, 1970; Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: Gabatarwa a Kan Jam'iyyun Ma'aikata (Littafi na Farko), Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: Gabatarwa Kan Sha'anin Yin Shawara Tattare (Littafi Na Biyu), 1959; Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: Industrial Estates, 1965; Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
    Author: Nigeria Trade Journal
  - Item 11: National Development Plan, 1965; Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Item 12: Nigeria Trades with the World, 1965; Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Item 13: Nigeria: A Study in Hypocrisy, 1968; Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
    Author: George T. Orick
  - Item 14: Nigeria: Slow Road to Trouble, 1962; Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Item 15: Packaging Industry, 1965; Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Item 16: Progress of Commercial Aviation in Nigeria, 1964; Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Item 17: Sawmill Industry in Nigeria, 1965; Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Item 18: Security Printing and Minting in Nigeria, 1965; Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Item 19: A Financial Institution for Africa, 1965; Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Item 20: Electricity Supply in Nigeria, 1965; Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Item 21: Water Resources of Nigeria, 1965; Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Item 22: Farm Settlement Scheme in Nigeria, 1962; Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Item 23: Nigeria :An Economic Survey, 1966; Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Item 24: Vocational Instructor and Supervisor Training: Nigeria, 1968; Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
    Author: International Labour Organisation
- Box: 20, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The History of the Carpenters' Dispute, 1949: Communist Activities Exposed, Publication (Box 20, Folder 15)
    Author: New Zealand Federation of Labor
  - Item 2: Social Security: Monetary Benefits and War Pensions in New Zealand, 1946; Publication (Box 20, Folder 15)
    Author: New Zealand. Social Security Dept.
  - Item 3: Social Security: Monetary Benefits and War Pensions in New Zealand, 1948; Publication (Box 20, Folder 15)